Guide to the Vice President for Student Affairs records, 1923-[ongoing] UA.09.02.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession A86-76, 7
  - Pilot Freshman Advising Project, 1979 (Box 48)
  - Provost Agreement, 1968-1980 (Box 48)
  - Provost, Office of, 1970-1980 (Box 48)
  - N. C. Public Interest Research Group (PIRG), 1973-1980 (Box 48)
  - Public Safety, Traffic, 1970-1980 (Box 48)
  - Quadrangle, Problems on, 1974-1980 (Box 48)
  - Quadrangle Pictures, 1970-1980 (Box 48)
  - Quail Roost Conference (on the Status of Undergraduate Education in the Arts and Sciences), 1971 (Box 48)
  - Racism Workshop, 1972 (Box 48)
  - Registrar, Office of, 1972-1980 (Box 49)
  - Regulations, 1969-1970 (Box 49)
  - Residential Life, Office of, 1974-1980 (Box 49)
  - Residential Life Committee, 1971-1979; 3 folders (Box 49)
  - Residential Staff, 1979-1980 (Box 49)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1970 (Box 49)
  - ROTC, 1969-1980 (Box 49)
  - Sailing Club, 1971-1980 (Box 49)
  - Sales, Solicitations, Deliveries on Campus, 1971-1976 (Box 50)
  - Sanford, Terry: President, 1975-1980 (Box 50)
  - Sanford, Terry: President, 1969-1974 (Box 50)
  - Scheduling Conflicts, Ad hoc Committee on, 1976 (Box 50)
  - Scholarships, Correspondence, 1970-1980 (Box 50)
  - Secretaries, 1971-1974 (Box 50)
  - Segregated Facilities, 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Senior Class Representatives, 1975-1978 (Box 50)
  - Sex Education, Committee on, 1973-1975 (Box 50)
  - Sex Information, 1969-1972 (Box 50)
  - "Sit-in Study": Allen Building (Box 50)
  - Student House for Academic & Residential Experimentation (SHARE), 1971-1973 (Box 50)
  - Social Fraternal Organizations: Policies & Procedures, 1979 (Box 50)
  - Sociology Majors Union, 1980 (Box 50)
  - Sororities, 1974-1979 (Box 50)
  - Speaker Ban Law, undated (Box 50)
  - Student Activities, 1972-1980 (Box 50)
  - Student Activities, Agency Accounts, 1974-1980 (Box 51)
  - Student Activities Van, 1970-1981 (Box 51)
  - Student Affairs Staff: Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box 51)
  - Student Affairs: Extended Staff, 1974-1976 (Box 51)
  - Student Affairs: Programmatic Staff, 1976-1980 (Box 51)
  - Student Affairs: Residential Life Staff, 1975-1980 (Box 51)
  - Student Concerns Survey, 1974-1976 (Box 51)
  - Student Conduct & In Loco Parentis, 1969-1970 (Box 51)
  - Study Abroad Programs, 1975-1980 (Box 51)
  - Summer Performing Arts, 1978-1984 (Box 51)
  - Summer Session, Ad hoc Committee on, 1979 (Box 51)
  - Summer Session, 1972-1980 (Box 51)
  - Summer Theater Program Committee, 1972-1980 (Box 52)
  - Telephones, 1970-1980 (Box 52)
  - Tennis, 1970-1976 (Box 52)
  - "Title IX" Regulations (Sex Discrimination), 1974-1980 (Box 52)
  - Transportation Management Board, 1979-1980 (Box 52)
  - Triangle Dance Guild, 1976-1979 (Box 52)
  - Trinity College, Office of Dean, 1971-1980; 2 folders (Box 52)
  - Trinity College Council, Proposed, 1980 (Box 53)
  - Trustees, Board of, 1969-1980 (Box 191)
    Board of Trustees restricted until 2030.
  - Undergraduate Education, 1964-1978 (Box 53)
  - Underground College Review, 1972 (Box 53)
  - United Fund, 1969-1979 (Box 53)
  - University Architect, 1975-1980 (Box 53)
  - University Counsel, 1972-1980 (Box 53)
  - University Forum, 1980 (Box 53)
  - University Judicial Board, 1970-1976 (Box 53)
  - University Planning Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 53)
  - University Planning Committee: Subcommittee on Athletics & Physical Education, 1972 (Box 53)
  - University Planning Committee: Subcommittee on Fine Arts, 1971-1972 (Box 53)
  - University Planning Committee: Subcommittee on Non-curricular Life, 1972 (Box 53)
  - University Policy: Off Campus Activities & Liability & Insurance, 1972-1973 (Box 53)
  - University Scheduling of Rooms, 1975-1980 (Box 53)
  - University Union: Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 54)
  - University Union: Correspondence, 1977 (Box 54)
  - University Union: Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 54)
  - University Union: Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 54)
  - University Union: Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 54)
  - University Union: "Reunion", 1976-1978 (Box 54)
  - University Union Board (1 of 4), 1971-1980 (Box 54)
  - University Union Board (2-4 of 4), 1971-1980; 3 folders (Box 55)
  - University Union: Executive Committee, 1973-1980 (Box 55)
  - University Union: Drama Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 55)
  - University Union: Facilities Committee, 1970-1980 (Box 55)
  - University Union: Finance Committee, 1976-1980 (Box 55)
  - University Union: Policy Committee, 1974-1980 (Box 56)
  - University Union: Game Room, 1974-1979 (Box 56)
  - University Union: Arts & Crafts Workshop, 1973-1980 (Box 56)
  - University Union: Graphic Arts Committee, 1969-1980 (Box 56)
  - University Union: Major Attractions Committee, 1974-1980 (Box 56)
  - University Union: Major Speakers Committee, 1970-1980 (Box 56)
  - University Unión: Performing Arts Committee, 1972-1980 (Box 56)
  - University Union: Program Advisor, 1967-1980 (Box 56)
  - University Union: Student Director, 1970-1975 (Box 56)
  - University Union: Xerox Operation, 1973-1975 (Box 56)
  - University Center Advisory Committee (1 of 2), 1978-1982 (Box 56)
  - University Center Advisory Committee (2 of 2), 1978-1982 (Box 57)
  - Educational Facilities Subcommittee on University Center, 1970-1977; 2 folders (Box 57)
  - University Center Planning Committee, 1975-1979 (Box 57)
  - University Union Planning Committee, 1971 (Box 57)
  - University Union (New) Construction, 1970-1973 (Box 57)
  - Use of Main Quadrangle, 1972-1975 (Box 57)
  - University Union: H. Wagoner Memorial, 1979-1980 (Box 57)
  - University Union: SPUD, 1975-1977 (Box 58)
  - Use of University Facilities, 1971-1980 (Box 58)
  - Van Service, Late Night, 1976-1980 (Box 58)
  - Visitation Regulations, 1969-1974 (Box 58)
  - Volunteers In Service to America, 1969-1971 (Box 58)
  - War/Anti-War Activities, 1971 (Box 58)
  - Women's Crew, 1975-1981 (Box 58)
  - WATS (Wide Area telephone service), 1972-1976 (Box 58)
  - West Campus Community Council, 1969-1971 (Box 58)
  - Who's Who, 1970-1974 (Box 58)
  - YM/YWCA, 1969-1980 (Box 58)
  - YM/YWCA: "The University Experience", 1970-1975 (Box 58)
  - YM/YWCA: "The Whole Earth Catalog", 1972 (Box 58)
  - YM/YWCA Advisory Board, 1972-1975 (Box 58)
  - ASDU Correspondence, 1962-1971 (Box 58)
  - ASDU Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 59)
  - ASDU Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 59)
  - ASDU: Budget and Funding, 1972-1980 (Box 59)
  - ASDU Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 59)
  - Chapel: Administrative Committee of the Chapel, 1962-1975; 2 folders (Box 60)
  - Chapel: Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 60)
  - Chapel: Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box 60)
  - Chapel: Faculty Associates, 1976-1981 (Box 60)
  - Chapel: Jordan Building, 1974-1984 (Box 60)
  - Chapel: Minister to the University, 1972-1981 (Box 60)
  - Chapel: Assistant Minister to the University, 1979-1981 (Box 60)
  - Chapel: Associate Minister to the University, 1973-1978 (Box 60)
  - Chapel Rehabilitation/Renovation Committee, 1969-1977 (Box 61)
  - Chapel: Sermons, 1969-1972 (Box 61)
  - Chapel: Committee to Honor John Blackburn, 1980-1981 (Box 61)
  - Chapel: Committee to Recognize Robert Young, 1983-1983 (Box 61)
  - Chapel: Council on Religious Life, 1979-1982 (Box 61)
  - Chapel: Use of Baptist Center and Westminster House, 1972-1977 (Box 61)
  - Chapel: Parish Ministry Advisory Committee, 1974-1980 (Box 61)
  - Chapel: Choral Activities, 1971-1981 (Box 61)
  - Publications Board: notebook, circa 1970 (Box 61)
  - Publications Board: Bassett Committee, 1973-1979 (Box 61)
  - Publications Board: Agendas & Announcements of Meetings, 1973-1981; 2 folders (Box 62)
  - Publications Board: Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 62)
  - Publications Board: Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 62)
  - Publications Board: Composition Shop, 1970-1977 (Box 62)
  - Publications Board: Print Shop, 1971-1975 (Box 62)
  - Publications Board: 1971 yearbook study survey, 1971-1971 (Box 62)
  - Publications Board: Chanticleer, 1970-1980; 2 folders (Box 63)
  - Publications Board: Chanticleer, 1972 (Box 63)
  - Publications Board: Chronicle, 1973-1980; 2 folders (Box 63)
  - Student Health Advisory Committee: Meetings and Agenda, 1970-1981 (Box 63)
  - Student Health Advisory Committee: membership lists, 1971-1981 (Box 64)
  - Student Health Advisory Committee: Correspondence, 1966-1980 (Box 64)
  - Student Health Advisory Committee: minutes, 1970-1981 (Box 64)
  - Student Health, Ad hoc Committee on, 1971-1974 (Box 64)
  - Student Health: Correspondence, 1970-1980 (Box 64)
  - Student Health Service: Human Sexuality Committee, 1973 (Box 64)
  - Student Accident and Sickness Insurance: General Correspondence, 1971-1980 (Box 64)
  - Student Mental Health Service, 1960-1977 (Box 65)
  - Student Mental Health: Questionnaire Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 65)
- Accession A91-69, 8
  This series includes materials from William Griffith's time as Vice President for Student Affairs. Files are partially alphabetical and include correspondence, reports, memorandums, printed materials, and other materials related to protests, demonstrations, and demands from African American students; the Arts and Sciences Campaign in the 1980s; the Publications Board; the Health, Physical Education, and Recreation department; several administrative search committees; proceedings of the Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU); and other topics.
  - AIESEC, 1966-1970 (Box 65)
  - Administration and Faculty, 1962-1969 (Box 65)
  - Administrative Reorganization, 1968-1970 (Box 65)
  - Block-Booking, 1963-1984 (Box 65)
  - Committee of Twelve, 1969 (Box 65)
  - Committee on Judicial Procedures: Pye and Watson Reports, 1969 (Box 65)
  - Cornell University: Residential Environment Material, 1968-1969 (Box 65)
  - Correspondence: Joe Martin Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 65)
  - Correspondience: Marcus Hobbs Miscellaneous, 1969-1970 (Box 65)
  - Dean of Student Affairs Staff, 1965-1970 (Box 65)
  - Coordinate College, 1965 (Box 66)
  - Duke Forum: Sound-Off Night, 1965 November 04 (Box 66)
  - IFC Report on Residential Life, 1969 (Box 66)
  - Judicial Board Members and Assistants, 1969 December 31 (Box 66)
  - Radio Program, 1964-1965 (Box 66)
  - Red Friars, 1965-1967 (Box 66)
  - Report: Judicial Trend Toward Student Academic Freedom - Van Alstyne, undated (Box 66)
  - Sit-In Hospital, 1970 January 21 (Box 66)
  - Sit-In Hospital, 1970 January 21 (Box 191)
    FERPA and Personnel restricted until 2040
  - Speakers Policy, 1968 (Box 66)
  - University Union: Miscellaneous Correspondence/Contracts, 1969-1970 (Box 66)
  - Publications Board: Journalism Course 103, 1966-1968 (Box 66)
  - Publications Board: Constitutions & Bylaws (old), 1959-1970 (Box 66)
  - Publications Board: Elections, 1962-1969 (Box 191)
    FERPA restricted until 2039.
  - Publications Board: Enterprise, 1968-1972 (Box 66)
  - Publications Board: Financial Statements, 1962-1970 (Box 66)
  - Publications Board: Financial General, 1964-1969 (Box 67)
  - Publications Board: Financial Salaries, 1961-1968 (Box 67)
  - Publications Board: Financial Budget Proposals, 1965-1971 (Box 67)
  - Publications Board: Executive Committee Minutes, 1962-1968 (Box 67)
  - Publications Board: Archive, 1960-1969 (Box 67)
  - Publications Board: "The Bantling", 1966 (Box 67)
  - Publications Board: "Chanticleer", 1961-1969 (Box 67)
  - Publications Board: Chronicle Correspondence & Reports, 1961-1968 (Box 67)
  - Publications Board Chronicle Reorganization Plan, 1968-1969 (Box 67)
  - Publications Board: Chronicle Circulation, 1962-1968 (Box 67)
  - Publications Board: Chronicle Enterprise System, 1968-1970 (Box 67)
  - Publications Board: Chronicle Obscenity Case, 1968 (Box 67)
  - Publications Board: "Peer", 1961-1969 (Box 67)
  - Publications Board: "Playbill", 1961-1966 (Box 67)
  - Publications Board: "Rubbish", undated (Box 67)
  - Publications Board: 'the real world', 1965-1966 (Box 67)
  - Publications Board: Tone and Quality of Publications, 1966 (Box 67)
  - Publications Board: Lecture Series (Bassett), 1963-1968 (Box 67)
  - Publications Board: Wm. Blackburn Literary Festival, 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Publications Board: Membership Lists, 1960-1972 (Box 68)
  - Academic Plan, 1987; 2 folders (Box 68)
  - Aeolian Organ, Advisory Committee for, 1986-1989; 2 folders (Box 68)
  - Afro-American Society, 1968-1969 (Box 68)
  - Afro-American Society (materials removed), 1968-1969 (Box 191)
  - Afro-American Society, 1969-1970 (Box 68)
  - Afro-American Society: African and Afro-American Studies Program, 1968-1969 (Box 69)
  - Afro-American Society Demonstrations, 1969\ (Box 69)
    Includes an account of the events of the Allen Building Takeover by a student witness from outside the building.
  - Allen Building Takeover by Black Students, 1969 (Box 69)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse (1-3 of 4), 1981-1988; 3 folders (Box 69)
  - Alcohol and Drug Abuse (4 of 4), 1981-1988 (Box 70)
  - Alcoholic Beverages, 1958-1987; 4 folders (Box 70)
  - Alumni Affairs (1 of 4), 1982-1990 (Box 70)
  - Alumni Affairs (2-4 of 4), 1982-1990; 3 folders (Box 71)
  - Alumni Affairs: Class of '50 Reunion, 1973-1990 (Box 71)
  - Alumni Affairs Tour, 1982-1990 (Box 71)
  - Alumni Summer Jobs Program, 1979-1982 (Box 71)
  - Apartheid/South Africa Coalition (1 of 3), 1985-1986 (Box 71)
  - Apartheid/South Africa Coalition (2-3 of 3), 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box 72)
  - Athletic Department, 1966-1985; 2 folders (Box 72)
  - Beta Theta Pi Fraternity (1-2 of 3), 1980-1991; 2 folders (Box 72)
  - Beta Theta Pi Fraternity (3 of 3), 1980-1991 (Box 73)
  - Beta Theta Pi 50th Reunion, 1987-1989 (Box 73)
  - Black Student Alliance, 1969-1975; 2 folders (Box 73)
  - British/American Festival, 1984-1984 (Box 73)
  - Carolina Friends School Committee Advisory Council, 1983-1988 (Box 73)
  - CBS TV Special, 1982-1987 (Box 73)
  - Chancellor, Office of, 1975-1979 (Box 191)
    FERPA and personnel restricted until 2049.
  - Chancellor, Office of (1 of 2), 1975-1990 (Box 73)
  - Chancellor, Office of (2 of 2), 1975-1990 (Box 74)
  - Chancellor's Committee: Instruction in Arts (Applewhite Report), 1980 (Box 74)
  - Chancellor's 'Directions for Progress', 1980 (Box 74)
  - Response of Student Affairs to "Directions for Progress", 1981 (Box 191)
    Board of Trustees restriction until 2031.
  - Chancellor, Office of -- Executive Officers' Report, 1985; 2 folders (Box 74)
  - Chancellor's Task Force on Residential Life, 1980 (Box 74)
  - Residential Life Task Force, 1979-1980; 2 folders (Box 74)
  - Chapel Basement Renovation, 1979-1980 (Box 74)
  - Response of Student Affairs to Task Force on Residential Life, 1980-1981 (Box 75)
  - Response to Residential Life Report, 1980-1981; 3 folders (Box 75)
  - Commencement Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 75)
  - Committee on Residence Hall Overcrowding, 1984 (Box 75)
  - Committee to Study Residence Hall Overcrowding (for Pres. Sanford) (1 of 3), 1984 (Box 75)
  - Committee to Study Residence Hall Overcrowding (for Pres. Sanford) (2-3 of 3), 1984; 2 folders (Box 76)
  - Conferences: Airport, 1977-1982 (Box 76)
  - Conferences: Ivy ACRC, 1980-1982; 2 folders (Box 76)
  - Counseling and Psychological Services -- Correspondence, 1979-1985; 2 folders (Box 76)
  - Counseling and Psychological Services -- Correspondence, 1979-1985 (Box 191)
    Board of Trustees restriction until 2035.
  - Development Office, 1981-1985; 2 folders (Box 77)
  - Development Office: Arts and Sciences Campaign, 1987-1991; 2 folders (Box 192)
    Donor restriction until 2061.
  - Development Office: Arts and Sciences Campaign Policies & Procedures Manual, 1986; 2 folders (Box 192)
    Donor restricted until 2056.
  - Development Office: Arts and Sciences Campaign - Faculty/Staff Campaign, 1985 (Box 192)
    Donor restricted until 2055.
  - Development Office: Arts and Sciences Campaign Endowment Proposals (1 of 2), 1983-1988 (Box 192)
    Donor restriction until 2058.
  - Development Office: Arts and Sciences Campaign Endowment Proposals (2 of 2), 1983-1988 (Box 193)
    Donor restricted until 2058.
  - Development Office: Arts and Sciences Campaign - Faculty/Staff Campaign, 1985-1986 (Box 193)
  - Development Office: Arts and Sciences Fundraising Group, 1981-1987; 4 folders (Box 193)
    Donor restriction until 2057.
  - Development Office: Cleveland Campaign, 1984-1985 (Box 194)
    Donor restriction until 2055.
  - Development Office: Campaign for Duke, 1989-1990 (Box 77)
  - Development Office: Duke Seminar, 1983-1990; 2 folders (Box 77)
  - Development Office: East/West Campaign, 1981-1983 (Box 77)
  - Dining Halls: Correspondence (1 of 2), 1981-1985 (Box 77)
  - Dining Halls: Correspondence (2 of 2), 1981-1985 (Box 78)
  - Douthat, Dean James, 1975-1990 (Box 78)
  - Duke Futures, 1985-1990 (Box 78)
  - Dukes and Duchesses, 1978-1983 (Box 78)
  - Durham Arts Council, 1981-1990 (Box 78)
  - Dutemple Scholarship, 1975-1979 (Box 78)
  - East Campus Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 78)
  - East Campus Council of Presidents, 1980-1981 (Box 78)
  - English-Speaking Union: National Council Meeting, 1983-1984 (Box 78)
  - Federations, 1975-1982 (Box 78)
  - Ferrer Investigation, 1982-1983 (Box 79)
  - Five Year Planning, 1987; 4 folders (Box 79)
  - Freshman Cluster Task Force, 1981-1982 (Box 79)
  - Freshman Committee, 1980 (Box 79)
  - Griffith, William J. (1 of 2), 1967-1991 (Box 79)
  - Griffith, William J. (2 of 2), 1967-1991 (Box 80)
  - "Guide to Duke", 1984-1985 (Box 80)
  - Health, Physical Education & Recreation, Department of, 1984-1985; 2 folders (Box 80)
  - Health, Physical Education & Recreation, Department of (1-2 of 3), 1981-1983; 2 folders (Box 80)
  - Health, Physical Education & Recreation, Department of (3 of 3), 1981-1983 (Box 81)
  - Health, Physical Education & Recreation, Advisory Committee on, 1981-1983 (Box 81)
  - Health, Physical Education & Recreation -- Correspondence re: Facilities and Grounds, 1973-1987; 4 folders (Box 81)
  - Health, Physical Education & Recreation: Correspondence re: Facilities and Grounds: oversize, 1984 (Oversize-folder 1)
    Floor plan of Card Gymnasium pool area renovation and locker room renovation
  - Health, Physical Education & Recreation: Miscellaneous: HPER Basic Data, 1980 (Box 82)
  - Health, Physical Education & Recreation: Miscellaneous: task force and committees, 1973-1975 (Box 82)
  - Health, Physical Education & Recreation: Miscellaneous: Task Force Report and Responses, 1974 (Box 82)
  - Health, Physical Education & Recreation: Miscellaneous: HPER, 1979 (Box 82)
  - Health, Physical Education & Recreation: Miscellaneous: Some data we have gathered, 1980 (Box 82)
  - Health, Physical Education & Recreation: Intramural Program, 1980-1985 (Box 82)
  - Health, Physical Education & Recreation: Sports Clubs (1-3 of 4), 1979-1986; 3 folders (Box 82)
  - Health, Physical Education & Recreation: Sports Clubs (4 of 4), 1979-1986 (Box 83)
  - Housing: Central Campus Apartments, 1981-1985; 2 folders (Box 83)
  - Housing: Central Campus Study Committee, 1983-1985; 2 folders (Box 83)
  - Housing: Damages in Residence Halls, 1980-1984 (Box 83)
  - Housing: New Dormitory, 1981-1983; 2 folders (Box 84)
  - Housing Management, Office of, 1982-1985 (Box 84)
  - Human Resource Effectiveness: President's Seminar, 1983-1985 (Box 84)
  - International House, 1981-1985; 2 folders (Box 84)
  - Korean Church, undated (Box 84)
  - Mail and Package Delivery, 1981-1985 (Box 84)
  - Minority Affairs, Office of (1 of 2), 1980-1991 (Box 84)
  - Minority Affairs, Office of (2 of 2), 1980-1991 (Box 85)
  - Minority Affairs (Black Affairs Office), 1974-1978; 2 folders (Box 85)
  - Minority Affairs: Summer Transitional Program (STP), 1981-1986; 2 folders (Box 85)
  - Murphy Center Endowment Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 85)
  - Music: Miscellaneous, 1976-1985 (Box 85)
  - Nixon Library, 1981 (Box 86)
  - Obituaries, 1969-1990 (Box 86)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa (ODK), 1979-1991; 2 folders (Box 86)
  - Orientation: Freshman, 1981-1985; 2 folders (Box 86)
  - Overcrowding, Advisory Committee on, 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box 86)
  - Page Auditorium, 1978-1985 (Box 87)
  - Panhellenic Council, 1981-1985 (Box 87)
  - Photography Club, 1979-1985 (Box 87)
  - Placement Services, 1986-1990; 4 folders (Box 87)
  - Placement Services, 1981-1985; 2 folders (Box 88)
  - Placement Services: Career Apprenticeship Program, 1980-1987 (Box 88)
  - Presidential Search Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 88)
  - President's Committee on Residential Life (Spragens' Committee), 1985 (Box 88)
  - Project Pride, 1977-1982 (Box 88)
  - Project WILD, 1977-1978; 2 folders (Box 88)
  - Project WILD: Board of Advisors, 1977-1988; 2 folders (Box 88)
  - Project WILD: Correspondence, 1980-1985; 2 folders (Box 89)
  - Project WILD: Correspondence, 1974-1980; 3 folders (Box 89)
  - Project WILD Manual (1 of 2), 1980-1983 (Box 89)
  - Project WILD Manual (2 of 2), 1980-1983 (Box 90)
  - Provost, Office of, 1981-1985; 3 folders (Box 90)
  - Public Safety Office, 1973-1985; 2 folders (Box 90)
  - Public Safety Office: Incident Reports, 1981-1990 (Box 91)
  - Red Friars, 1970-1983 (Box 91)
  - Research Triangle International Visitors Center, 1982-1983 (Box 91)
  - Residence Hall Educational Philosophy, Ad hoc Committee to Discuss, 1981-1985 (Box 91)
  - Residence Hall Study Space, 1980 April 3 (Box 91)
  - Residential Judicial Board, 1978-1988 (Box 91)
  - Residential Judicial Board Decisions, 1983-1988 (Box 91)
  - Residential Life Committee, 1980-1985 (Box 91)
  - Residential Life Implementation Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 91)
  - Residential Programming (1 of 3), 1980-1985 (Box 91)
  - Residential Programming (2-3 of 3), 1980-1985; 2 folders (Box 92)
  - Residential Staff (Resident Advisors), 1981-1985 (Box 92)
  - Sailing Club, 1981-1985 (Box 92)
  - Sanford, President Terry, 1981-1989 (Box 92)
  - Scheduling Conflicts, ad hoc Committee on, 1981-1986 (Box 92)
  - Search Committee, Assistant Dean of the Chapel, 1990-1991 (Box 92)
  - Search Committee, Dean for Student Life, 1980-1981 (Box 92)
  - Search Committee, Director, Career Development Center, 1989-1990 (Box 92)
  - Search Committee, Director, Career Development Center: Candidate Evaluations, 1989-1990 (Box 92)
  - Search Committee, Director of Chapel Music, 1988-1990 (Box 92)
  - Search Committee, Director of Debate, 1986-1987 (Box 93)
  - Search Committee, Director, International House, 1983-1986 (Box 93)
  - Search Committee, Director, Mary Lou Williams Center for Black Culture, 1983 (Box 93)
  - Search Committee, Director, Office of Cultural Affairs, 1984 (Box 93)
  - Search Committee, Executive V-P (Business, Finance, Law), 1984 (Box 93)
  - Search Committee, Minister to the University, 1983-1984 (Box 93)
  - Search Committee, Director, University Union, 1974-1975 (Box 93)
  - Search Committee, Vice President for Student Affairs, 1990-1991 (Box 93)
  - Self-Study: Report by the Self-Study Visitation Committee of the Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1965 October 10-13 (Box 93)
  - Self Study: Report of the Fifth-Year Reaffirmation of Institutional Self-Study, 1971 August (Box 93)
  - Self-Study: University of Miami (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 93)
  - Self-Study: University of Miami (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 94)
  - Space Allocation Committee (Flowers/Union/Page Buildings), 1980-1983; 2 folders (Box 94)
  - Sky Devils Club, 1978 (Box 206)
    FERPA restricted until 2048.
  - Skydevils Club, 1985-1986 (Box 94)
  - Squash/Racquetball Committee, 1982 (Box 94)
  - Student Activities, Office of, 1981-1985; 2 folders (Box 94)
  - Student Activities: Quad Activity Policy, 1977-1982 (Box 94)
  - Student Affairs Intern, 1976-1980 (Box 94)
  - Student Affairs Leadership Assistance Program, 1981-1985 (Box 95)
    Program formerly referred to as Provost's Agreement
  - Student Affairs Leadership Assistance Program, 1981-1985 (Box 194)
    FERPA restricted until 2055.